Hey guys, I want to ask y'all to do me a favor when you watch my videos.
The first thing I want you to do is I want you to take a moment to take your emotions out of the video.
I know it's just me talking to you like this, but I'm really talking to a phone, not directly to you.
Second, I want you to really watch the video twice.
Not for views, but actually for context and the words being used.
I don't choose words all willy-nilly, okay?
So every word in there is there for a reason.
And I feel like a lot of times folks skip over some words to get other words and then start giving me all the words in the comments.
And it ain't even relative to what I've actually been saying.
I think a lot of men who are in a more traditional mindset around relationships feel like they got to have respect more than love.
See, like right there, I said traditional men.
But some of y'all just heard men.
And the third thing I want you to do is if you like what I said, share it.
Because at the end of the day, we are fighting a culture of idiocy.
And when we see common sense, we got to spread it because knowledge is wealth.
So let's do it again.
So let's do it, please.
What do you say, get it?
Thank you.